All the articles
were sorted out
Yeah
His agency worked hard
Their damage might be
more serious than us
How have you been?
I just…
monitored the dramas
And… I'm moving out
You're moving?
Yes
My rent contract
is expiring soon
and I found a house
in a good location
I'm sorry, Soobin
You know what?
You were the only one
who I liked in my life
Still, I have to say this
Don't see Shin Yoo-il
anymore
Being with him
puts you in danger
It's not easy to have
a fake relationship
and coming out
is not either
Shin Yoo-il was willing
to take that risk
only if he'd go viral
in the first place
If necessary, he could
cancel that contract
and leave you any time
Hyesung
I don't want you
to get hurt
I'm saying this
as your friend